>> Brian Holt: 现在，我将向您展示如何使此电子邮件变得轻松一点。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Now, I'm gonna show you how
to make this email a little bit easier.
所以当你写 " React " 时，写道具点很快就会变得非常老了，
So writing props dot gets very old very
quickly when you're writing React, so
有一件事你可以称之为破坏
there's a thing that you can
do called destructuring.
所以我能做的是我能取代道具
So what I can do here
is I can replace props,
我知道这东西会被称为动物，品种和名称，对吧 ?
I know that the thing is gonna be
called animal, breed, and name, right?
所以我就能把它拉出来所以我要把道具都删掉
So I can actually just pull this out,
so I'm gonna delete props here,
把括号放在后面
put the parentheses back.
然后在里面我要放大括号就像这样
And then inside of that,
I'm gonna put curly brackets, like that.
然后我要说名字
And then I'm gonna say name,
像这样繁殖的动物
animal, and breed like that.
这将会把这些特别命名的属性拉出来
And this is going to pull out these
particularly named properties within these
并使它们作为变量名可用，对吗 ?
objects and make them available
as those variable names, right?
所以不要说我的名字我只想说名字
So instead of saying props.name,
I'm just gonna say name.
> > Brian Holt: 和动物一样
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Same
thing here with animal,
>> Brian Holt: 并繁殖。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And breed.
>> Brian Holt: 有道理吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Makes sense?
它被称为破坏， >> Brian Holt:
It's called destructuring,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And
一切都应该以同样的方式运作
everything should work the same way,
which it does.
>> Brian Holt: 好， >> Brian Holt: 因此
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
那是第一部分
that's the first section.
恭喜你你知道现在有点反应了
So congratulations,
you know a little bit of React now.
好消息是它是最重要的。
And the good news is this
is kind of most of it.
我要给你们看一堆其他的东西，对吧 ?
I'm going to show you a bunch
of other stuff, right?
我得赚他们付我的钱 [LAUGH]
I have to earn what they're
paying me [LAUGH] but
这有点像是 React 的核心思想
this is kinda like the core
idea of what React is.
> > Brian Holt: 所以这里有一个落实点，所以如果你落后了
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So there's a commit point
here, so if you're falling behind and
你想站在这一点上你就能在第一次
you wanna come up to this point, you can
actually just move to the first commit in
这就把你带到车间里去了
the repo, and this will take you
to this point in the workshop.
接下来我们要做的就是开始引入一些工具
The next thing we're gonna do is we're
going to start introducing some tooling to
救我们出去
help us out.
因为你不想这么写
Because you don't wanna
write React like this,
你可以让 React 更容易写作
you can actually make React
much easier to write.
但是，这还是雷法的核心概念。
But again, this is still the core
concepts of what React is.